Oneida Community Collection
Oneida Community Collection
- Manuscripts and personal papers
  - Aiken, Manley A., 1875; 1880 (Box 38)
    1875 Je 10 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Je 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1880 Ag 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Allen, Christine, 1891-1911 (Box 38)
    Misc. family correspondence
  - Allen, Emily H., 1852-1878 (Box 38)
    1852 S 3 to Marcus L. Worden
    S 13 to Marcus L. Worden
    1853 My 24 to Marcus L. Worden
    1872 My 12 to Beulah Hendee
    1878 Je 13 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    undated 4 letters to Marcus L. Worden
  - Allen, George D., 1878-1892 (Box 38)
    1878 Ap 1 to James W. Towner
    1886 N 12 to William A. Hinds
    1887 Ja 9 to William A. Hinds
    Mr 31 to William A. Hinds
    1888 F 28 Santa Ana property note
    1892 N 27 to William A. Hinds
  - Allen, Grosvenor N., 1893-1911 (Box 38)
    1893 N 5 to Dorothy Barron
    undated to Pierrepont B. Noyes (?)
    1895-1911 Misc. family correspondence
  - Allen, Harriet Eliza, 1902-1911 (Box 39)
    [no year] F 27 to Marcus L. Worden
    File of family correspondence
  - Allen, Henry, 1867; undated (Box 39)
    1867 O 16 to Marcus L. Worden
    O 24 to Marcus L. Worden
    Account of Henry Allen Sr. (4 p. w/ Hope Allen's notes)
  - Allen, Henry Grosvenor, 1866-1907 (Box 39)
    1866 Ag 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1871 Ap 22 to Mother (copy)
    1873 N 2 to Beulah Hendee
    1879 O 29 Marriage license (P.M. Underhill) (copy)
    N 1 'To the Family' (copy)
    1880 N 10 Receipt for 132 shares of O.C.L. stock (copy)
    N 10 Receipt to P.M. Underhill for purchase of 68 shares of O.C.L. stock (copy)
    1894 Je 3 to Judge G. A. Forbes--in George Campbell file
    1899-1904 Misc. family correspondence
    1905 Misc. family correspondence
    1906-1907 Misc. family correspondence
    [no year] S 14 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1878 Daybook
    1877-1879 Estimate Book
    1907 Ja Notes from O.C.L. Annual Banquet
  - Allen, Hope Emily, 1899-1912 (Box 40)
    Misc. correspondence
  - Bailey Family, 1875-1903? (Box 41)
    File of letters, primarily from Jane Bailey to Lily Cragin
  - Baker, Mary Victoria, 1879-1880 (Box 41)
    1879 N 2 to Harriet N. Olds
    N 11 to Harriet N. Olds
    N 18 to Harriet N. Olds
    D 5 to Harriet N. Olds
    D 11 to Harriet N. Olds
    D 26 to Harriet N. Olds
    D 27 to Harriet N. Olds
    1880 Ja 1 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Barron, Alfred, 1852-1893; undated (Box 41)
    See also Hendee-Barron
    1852 N 24 to Alvah and Fannie Barron
    1853 Mr 20 to Alvah and Fannie Barron
    1854 Ap 10 to Fannie Barron
    1855 Ap 27 to Fannie Barron
    1861 Ag 14 to Fannie Barron
    1863 Ja 4 to Alvah Barron
    1864 D 12 to J. Homer Barron
    1865 F 4 to Fannie Barron
    Mr 21 to Fannie Barron
    Ap 8 to Fannie Barron
    Ap 10 to Fannie Barron
    Je 15 to Fannie Barron
    1866 Je 22 to Fannie Barron
    O 10 to George E. Cragin
    O 26 to M. E. Kellogg
    1868 F 4 to Fannie Barron
    1876 N 29 to Maud K. Barron
    1878 D 27 from Hopson, Shepard (Utica) re: Shakespeare bust
    1879 Ja 3 invoice from Hopson, Shepard
    Mr 15 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Je 28 to Harriet H. Skinner
    Jl 17 to G.W. Hamilton
    O 23 to Harriet H. Skinner
    D 2 Marriage license (copy)
    D 17 Contract of marriage (Husband's copy)
    1880 Mr 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ap 2 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Jl 26 to Annie Hatch
    1882 O 26 to Maud K. Barron
    O 3 to James B. Herrick
    1883 Ja 18 to Maud K. Barron
    Mr 16 to Maud K. Barron
    My 12 to Maud K. Barron
    My 28 to Maud K. Barron
    My 28 Supoena for appearance at Vaill trial
    D 14 to Maud K. Barron
    1884 F 21 To Tirzah C. Miller
    Mr 22 to Maud K. Barron
    Ap 28 to Maud K. Barron
    Je 9 to Maud K. Barron
    1888 Ag 5 to Godfrey Noyes
    1889 D 30 to Maud K. Barron
    1890 D 9 to Maud K. Barron
    1891 Mr 26 to Maud K. Barron
    Ap 30 to Maud K. Barron
    My 7 to Maud K. Barron
    N 11 to Maud K. Barron
    S 8 to Maud K. Barron
    1892 Ap 17 to Maud K. Barron
    S 18 to Maud K. Barron
    O 20 to Maud K. Barron
    N 14 to Maud K. Barron
    D 8 to Maud K. Barron
    1893 Ja 30 to Maud K. Barron
    F 5 to Maud K. Barron
    Obituary
    Ja 29 to Tirzah C. Miller (copy)
    [no year] D 8 to Fannie Kinsley Barron
    v.d. Early records of the Barron family
    1870-1884 Incoming correspondence
    Includes correspondence re: Footnotes and correspondence from New York Tribune
    Footnotes scrapbook & list of book reviews
    Footnotes scrapbook taken from The Circular with Alfred Barron's mss. additions and corrections
  - Barron, Dorothy, 1889-1911 (Box 42)
    1889 Jl 6 to Hilda
    1889-1890 3 letters to Dorothy Barron from Milley?
    1906 Mr 5 to John Leonard
    1896 Jl 14 to Gertrude Noyes
    1910 S 12 to Mary and Catherine Leonard
    S 19 to Mary and Catherine Leonard
    S 22 to Mother Charlotte
    1911 D 15 to ? Noyes
    Miscellaneous poetry, sketches, etc.; includes The literary sextette (1891), a file of letters from Caroline Ebinger, a Shaker (1894-1925), and letters to Miriam T. Noyes (Earl)
  - Barron, J. Homer, 1876-1904 (Box 42)
    1876 Jl 31 to Tirzah C. Miller?
    1879 F 2 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1890-1904 File of letters to Maud K. Barron
  - Barron, Maria, 1893; undated (Box 42)
    1893 F 3 to Alfred Barron
    Ap 27 to Maud K. Barron
    My 24 to Maud K. Barron
    My 26 to Maud K. Barron
    1910 Ja 18 to Dorothy Barron Leonard re: William Tinsley
    [no year] Mr 11 to Alfred Barron and Beulah (Hendee) Barron
  - Barron, Maud K., 1892-1893; undated (Box 43)
    1892 D 11 to Alfred Barron
    1893 F 5 to Alfred Barron
    [no year] Je 16 to Alfred Barron
    undated Thurs to M. E. Kellogg
    'Recollections of children's occupations,' recorded by Hope E. Allen
    The care of children in 'The Oneida Community' (188-)
  - Barron, Minerva S., 1879; 1933,; undated (Box 43)
    1879 Marriage application, license, and certificate -- in John Norton file
    Miscellaneous reminiscences
    Recollections (1933)
  - Barron, Ruth, undated (Box 43)
    to George [W. Noyes?]
  - Bloom, Clarence, 1875; 1908 (Box 43)
    1875 Je 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1908 Ap 10 to William A. Hinds
  - Bloom, Sophia L. (Nunns), 1886 (Box 43)
    O 15 to William A. Hinds
  - Bolles, Rachel M., undated (Box 43)
    D 28 to Harriet Matthews
  - Bradley, Constance, 1871 (Box 43)
    Ag 28 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Bradley, Sarah, undated (Box 43)
    Jl 2 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    O 2 to Charlotte M. Leonard [with additional note by Harriet A. Noyes]
  - Bristol, Birdseye, 1850s (Box 43)
    My 26 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Burgess, L., 1852; undated (Box 43)
    1852 Je 8 to Marcus L. Worden
    Je 12 to Marcus L. Worden
    undated to Marcus L. Worden
  - Burnham, Abigail Scott, 1852; undated (Box 43)
    1854 Ja 23 to Edwin Burnham
    [no year] Jl 15 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Burnham, Almira, undated (Box 43)
    Criticism of Marcus L. Worden
  - Burnham, Edwin Scott, 1875 (Box 43)
    F 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Burnham, Evalyn A., 1903; 1909 (Box 43)
    1903 Je 8 to William A. Hinds
    Je 17 to William A. Hinds
    Je 23 to William A. Hinds
    N 19 to William A. Hinds
    1909 O 26 to William A. Hinds
  - Burnham, George Henry, 1870-1903 (Box 43)
    1870 Je 29 to John Humphrey Noyes [with John Humphrey Noyes's reply]
    1872 Ja 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Jl 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    0 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1903? Schedule of assignments of Geo. H. Burnham Co.
  - Burnham, Henry W., 1849-1887; undated (Box 43)
    1849 Je 10 to Marcus L. Worden
    1856 Ag 11 to Edwin Burnham
    1867 Je 17 to Brother [Silas Howard] (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1887 F 8 to William A. Hinds
    undated to ?
    undated Criticism of Marcus L. Worden
  - Burt, Abram L., 1886; undated (Box 43)
    1886 Ap 13 to Fidelia Burt
    Ap 15 to Fidelia Burt
    undated to Mrs. Bushnell
  - Burt, Charles A., 1871-1893; undated (Box 43)
    1871 Ja 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1873 Ja 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] Jl 11 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] S 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] S 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] S 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] S 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] Jl to Dear Sister [Tirzah C. Miller]
    [no year] Ag 15 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1893 Legal brief: Charles A. Burt vs. Oneida Community Ltd.
  - Burt, Edmund, 1852 (Box 43)
    Ja 16 to Jonathan Burt
  - Burt, Fidelia, 1869; undated (Box 43)
    1869 N 29 to Harriet N. Olds
    undated to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Burt, Jonathan, 1849-1851 (Box 43)
    1849 Ap 22 to Marcus L. Worden with G. Cragin letter (5/6/1849)
    My 5 to Marcus L. Worden
    1850 Ja 14 to Marcus L. Worden
    1851 N 11 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Burt, Lorinda Lee, 1876-1877 (Box 43)
    1876 Jl 4 to Harriet Matthews
    1877 Mr 26 to Harriet Matthews
    Mr 26 to Harriet Matthews
  - Bushnell, Candance B., 1864-1876; undated (Box 43)
    1864 Jl 18 to Brother [William G.] Kelly
    N 9 to Beulah Hendee
    N 18 to Beulah Hendee
    D 29 to Beulah Hendee
    1865 Mr 1 to Beulah Hendee
    1868 F 18 to Beulah Hendee
    1872 My 10 to Beulah Hendee
    1876 Mr 27 to Beulah Hendee
    Ag 26 to Beulah Hendee
    undated to Beulah Hendee
    [no year] S 4 to Beulah Hendee
    [no year] N 26 to Beulah Hendee
  - Campbell, Achsah, 1856 (Box 43)
    Ja 13 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Campbell, Emma A., 1847 (Box 43)
    Autograph album with entries by John Humphrey Noyes, Mary E. Cragin, John L. Skinner,Harriet H. Skinner, Stephen R. Leonard, Charlotte A. Miller, George Washington Noyes, and Julia (?)
  - Campbell, George, 1862-1894 (Box 43)
    1862 Ag 10 from Arthur Young
    1882 Ap 7 to James B. Herrick
    1894 Je 4 to Judge G. A. Forbes
  - Campbell, Sarah Burnham, 1856-1878; undated (Box 43)
    1856 Mr 4 to Edwin Burnham
    Ag 6 to Edwin Burnham
    N 23 to Edwin Burnham
    1864 Jl 24 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    1867 Jl 16 to Harriet N. Olds
    1873 Ja 13 to Harriet Matthews
    My 16 to Harriet Matthews
    1875 F 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Mr 11 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1876 Ap 20 to Harriet Matthews
    1877 O 17 to Harriet Matthews
    1878 Ja 8 to Emily Otis
    Ja 31 to Dorr Burnham
    Ap 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ap 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
    My 13 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Je 10 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Je 26 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    [no year] Mon. to Edwin Burnham
  - Carr, Amasa Whitney, 1852-1905 (Box 44)
    1852 My 3 to Marcus L. Worden
    [signed by O.C. 'kitchen folk')
    1905 O 6 to William A. Hinds
    N 5 to William A. Hinds
  - Conant, James A., 1867 (Box 44)
    Je 16 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Conant, Olive, 1850; 1879 (Box 44)
    1850 Ja 16 to Harriet Worden
  - Conant, Virtue, 1870; 1872 (Box 44)
    1870 Ap 20 to Harriet N. Olds
    1872 Ap 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Cook, Catherine, various dates (Box 44)
    File of letters to M. L. Worden and other Worden children
  - Cragin, Charles A., 1873-1880; undated (Box 44)
    1873 Ja 31 to H
    1876 Ag 7 to bill from Ocean House, Newport, R.I.
    1877 Ag 26 to Emily Otis
    0 16 to Viola Cragin
    1880 O 17 to Dear Friend [Mary?]
    [no year] My 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] S 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1874 Scrapbook of articles in The Circular
  - Cragin, George, 1849-1867 (Box 44)
    1849 Ja 5 to Marcus L. Worden
    My 1 to Marcus L. Worden
    My 9 to Marcus L. Worden
    1850 5 22 to Marcus L. Worden
    1851 Mr 8 to Marcus L. Worden
    Ap 1 to Marcus L. Worden
    1852 O 17 to Marcus L. Worden
    0 26 to Marcus L. Worden
    Je 8 to Marcus L. Worden (see L. Burgess)
    1854 Mr 5 to Silas and Naomi Howard (copy; original in
    Amherst College Library)
    1856 Ja 11 to Marcus L. Worden
    F 1 to Marcus L. Worden
    5 3 to Marcus L. Worden
    1867 Je 17 to Bro. Howard -- See H. W. Burnham
  - Cragin, George E., 1881-1882; 1914,; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 44)
      1881 N 9 to John and Lily [Cragin?]
      N 26 to John Cragin
      1882 F 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    - Writings (Box 44)
      'Biographical notes'
      'Bible communism and the press' (2 copies)
      'Goldwin Smith and Community culture'
      Reminiscences (unpublished?)
      Reminiscences (published in quadrangle, 1913-1914)
      Character sketches
  - Cragin, John Holton, undated (Box 44)
    'Christ's second coming took place immediately after the destruction of Jerusalem in A.D. 70' [Extracts with slight verbal alteration from letters to The Oneida Post]
  - Cragin, Mary E., 1847-1851; undated (Box 44)
    1847 entry in E.A. Campbell's Autograph album
    1849 Ja 5 to Marcus L. Worden (with G. Cragin's letter)
    1849 F 22 to Marcus L. Worden
    F 22 to Harriet H. Skinner
    1851 Mr 2 to Marcus L. Worden
    undated to Brother [Lovett?] (copy; original in Vermont Historical Society Library?)
  - Cragin, Viola, 1877 (Box 44)
    N 11 to Emily Otis
  - DeLatre, Herbert (Box 44)
    See also oil painting entitled 'Field Study' in Mansion House Library
    Sketch of Virtue Conant
    Photograph of untitled sketch (original in Jessie C. Kinsley's Album)
  - DeLatre, Robert Sparrow (Box 44)
    [no year] Ap 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Dunn, Fidelia, 1875 (Box 44)
    My 24 to Charlotte M. Leonard
  - Dunn, Marian A., 1872; 1873 (Box 44)
    1872 Ag 6 to Harriet N. Olds
    1873 Ap 10 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Dunn, Sarah K., 1878-1888; undated (Box 44)
    1878 My 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1879 Mr 13 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1882 D 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1888 Mr 11 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    [no year] Ap 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] Ap 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Earl, Miriam T., See Noyes, Miriam T.
  - Earl, Wilber Talcott (Box 45)
    'Memoirs of Wilber T. Earl, 1881-1960 (38 p. typescript)
  - Easton, Abel, 1878-1879 (Box 45)
    1878 Mr 23 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Mr 26 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Mr 30 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Ap 2 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Ap 9 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Ap 11 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Ap 18 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Jl 1 to John Humphrey Noyes
    1879 My 6 to John Humphrey Noyes
    My 12 to John Humphrey Noyes
    My 21 to John Humphrey Noyes
    My 25 telegram to Oneida Community
  - Frankland, Frederick W., See Hinds, William Alfred and Miller, George Noyes
  - Freeman, Herbert, 1894-1895 (Box 45)
    File of letters to Dorothy Barron
  - Freeman, John S., 1880; 1881 (Box 45)
    1880 5 21 to James B. Herrick
    O 16 to James B. Herrick
    O 17 to James B. Herrick
    O 20 to James B. Herrick
    O 21 to James B. Herrick
    O 30 to James B. Herrick
    N 20 to James B. Herrick
    N 30 to James B. Herrick
    D 9 to James B. Herrick
    1881 F 10 to James B. Herrick
  - Guiteau, Charles J., 1881; undated (Box 45)
    See also Pitt, T.L. and John Humphrey Noyes's Niagara Copybook (Box 67)
    1881 Guiteau vs. Oneida Community by John Humphrey Noyes; includes statements, depositions, documents, and transcriptions of letters
    Miscellaneous correspondence
    Published materials
    Clippings
  - Guiteau trial (Box 46)
    Clippings, Supreme Court Reports (2 vols.)
  - Hall, Harriet A., undated (Box 47)
    to Marcus L. Worden
  - Hamilton, Augusta, 1856-1879 (Box 47)
    1869 Ja 1 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Mr 8 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Mr 21 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Mr 28 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    1871 Ja 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1877 5 17 to Harriet Matthews
    1879 Mr 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Hamilton, Erastus Hapgood, 1851-1888; undated (Box 47)
    1851 Ja 28 to Marcus L. Worden
    1865 Ja 21 to Gerrit Smith (original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Collection)
    F 23 to Gerrit Smith (original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Collection
    1867 Mr 31 to Beulah Hendee
    1872 D 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1873 F 4 to G.D. Allen
    My 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
    u 1874 Ja 7 to Beulah Hendee
    Ja 29 to Beulah Hendee
    F 8 to Beulah Hendee
    N 22 to Tirzah C. Miller (typescript)
    1878 Je 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Je 11 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1879 Ja 16 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 26 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1884 Ap 2 to James B. Herrick
    Ap 2 to James B. Herrick
    Ag 20 to James B. Herrick
    1887 D 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1888 Mr 1 to Joseph Ackley
    Mr 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] Ja 24 (Thursday) to Marcus L. Worden
  - Hamilton, George W., 1876 (Box 47)
    My 4 to Harriet N. Olds
    My 14 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Hamilton, Harley, 1863; various dates (Box 47)
    Miscellaneous correspondence and music addressed to Dorothy Barron Leonard relating to her poem 'The Minuet'
    1863 Mr 8 'Agreement concerning Harley Hamilton' (copy; original in Hilda Herrick Noyes Coll.)
  - Hamilton, Philena Baker, 1872 (Box 47)
    Ap 15 to Mr. Miller
  - Hamilton, Rose, 1875-1876 (Box 47)
    1875 D 14 to Harriet N. Olds
    D 25 to Harriet N. Olds
    1876 Ja 4 to Harriet N. Olds
    Ja 31 to Harriet N. Olds
    Ap 27 to Harriet N. Olds
    Je 1 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Hamilton, Susan C., 1854 (Box 47)
    Ag 21 to Charlotte M. Leonard
  - Hatch, Annie, 1867-1885 (Box 47)
    1867 D 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1869 My 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1870 Ap 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1871 Mr 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1872 D to Alfred Barron (5 letters)
    1875 F 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
    My 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1878 5 20 to Dorothea Barron
    1879 Mr 7 to John Humphrey Noyes
    O 29 to Alfred Barron
    1874-1885 File of 126 letters to Beulah Hendee
  - Hatch, Eleazer L., 1847 (Box 47)
    O 24 to William H. Cook
  - Hawley Family, 1885-1908 (Box 47)
    File of letters to W. A. Hinds from California
  - Hawley, Elizabeth G., 1856-1902; undated (Box 47)
    1859 My 23 to Marcus L. Worden
    1872 Ap 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 14 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Je 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1873/4? to John Humphrey Noyes
    F 11 to Tirzah C. Miller
    F 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    F 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
    F 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
    F 22 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1877 Ja 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 11 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
    D 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    D 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1878 F 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 13 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 15 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 18 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1879 Ja 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ja 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ja 18 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ja 21 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ja 29 to Mary Louise Prindle
    F 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
    F 20 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Mr 19 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 2 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 13 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 26 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 30 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Je 24 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Je 29 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Jl 30 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Jl 31 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Jl 31 to Mr. Woolworth
    Ag 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 15 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 19 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 22 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1880 Jl 9 to William A. Hinds
    1903 Jl 8 to Beulah Hendee Barron
    [no year] Ag 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] Ag 18 to Mary Louise Prindle
    undated to Mary Louise Prindle (p. 5-6 only)
    1902 'A brief epitome of my first acquaintance with J. H. Noyes'
  - Hawley, Victor, 1876-1877 (Box 47)
    Diary (typescript)
  - Hayes, Rutherford Birchard, 1886 (Box 47)
    O 18 to Harriet H. Skinner
  - Hendee, Beulah, 1877-1898; undated (Box 48)
    1877-1885 File of 88 letters to Annie Hatch
    1879 poem
    1873 F 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
    F 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1876 Jl 11 to Harriet Matthews
    1879 F 8 to J. L. Sears
    My 11 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1898 F 20 to Herrick family
    1879 File of letters between Beulah Hendee and Alfred Barron
    undated Note on birthday of Dorothy [Barron] ('Jenny Wren')
    1879 D 17 Contract of marriage (wife's copy)
  - Herrick, James B.
    - Correspondence, 1865-1905; undated (Box 48)
      1865 Je 25 'Letter of withdrawal' to Rev. Horatio Potter (clipping)
      Jl 4 Rev. Horatio Potter's reply to James B. Herrick
      1867 Ja 24 to Alfred Barron
      187- draft letter to Stephen ? on revival work
      1870 5 27 to William A. Hinds
      N 9 to Helen C. Noyes
      1873 F 16 to Sophie [Bledsoe] Herrick with details of divorce arrangement
      1875 F 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1877 My 28 to Ann [Hobart]
      My 28 to James B. Herrick from C. Pelletier
      D 24 to members of "the Club"
      1878 Je 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 10 to James B. Herrick from ? (Paris, France)
      1879 F 8 to John Humphrey Noyes
      S 11 to Bishop Huntington
      S 18 Bishop Huntington's reply to James B. Herrick
      S 22 to Bishop Huntington (in S 11 letter)
      1881 Jl 3 to Mr. Hamilton
      Jl 31 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 26 Offer to buy Stone Cottage property
      1882 Mr 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1884 Ja 6 to Helen and her reply to 'Dear Sister'
      Ja 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ja 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1885 F 3 to [Cousin] Julia Chichester
      1886 Ja 31 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Mr 22 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1887 Ag 11 to Charles M. Kubell?
      Ag 17 to C. Howard Young
      Ag 19 to Nellie S. Hyde
      N 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 19 to O. B. Feuner?
      .
      D 30 to Theodore R. Noyes
      1888 form letter to inquirers to O.C.
      Mr 8 to ?
      Mr 17 to James [Vaill]
      Mr 17 to Mrs. Langstaff
      Jl 25 to Frederick W. Frankland
      Jl 27 to Frederick W. Frankland
      5 14 to Harriet A. Noyes
      1903 Ag 14 to George Noyes Miller
      1905 D 3 to Mr. Gignoux
      [no year] O 14 to Mrs. Skinner
      [no year] Mr 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
    - Writings (Box 48)
      List of J.B. Herrick's books brought in May 1868
      Healing miracles of Christ with Development of healing power in the Community
      Domestic accommodations
      How the offensive letter to Tirzah came to be written
      Frank story about Geo. E.
      Observations of J.B.H.
      Book review: H. Pyle's Rejected of men (1904)
      Pentacost on love (N 13, 1884)
      Memo on Shakers (undated)
      Undated fragments
      1880-82 miscellaneous letters in J. H. Noyes's Niagara Copybook (Box 67)
  - Herrick, Winifred, 1894 (Box 48)
    D 8 to Dorothy Barron
  - Higgins, Cornelius, 1855 (Box 48)
    F 8 to Silas and Naomi Howard
  - Higgins, Elmira, 1859; undated (Box 48)
  - Hillerman, Frances, 1871-1904 (Box 48)
    1871 5 19 to Libbie Kellogg
    1894 D 31 to Stephen R. Leonard (II)
    1904 Je 12 to William A. Hinds
  - Hinds, Elliot, 1895-1897 (Box 48)
    File of 20 letters to William A. Hinds
  - Hinds, William Alfred, 1857-1896; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 48)
      1857 O 18 to Marcus L. Worden
      1866 D 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1867 O 8 to Marcus L. Worden
      1870 D 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1872 Ja 10 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1875 F 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1876 Ja 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ja 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Jl 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
      S 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      D 6 to Tirzah C. Miller